let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is not a front-end technology?",
    answer: "SQL",
    options: [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "JavaScript",
      "SQL"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " The purpose of the Front-end framework in Full stack development is :",
    answer: "To provide the client-side interface",
    options: [
      "To provide the client-side interface",
      "To manage databse",
      "To reduce the server load",
      "To send http requests"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Of the following sort algorithms, which has execution time that is least dependent on initial ordering of the input ?",
    answer: "Merge sort",
    options: [
      "Selection sort",
      "Insertion sort",
      "Quick sort",
      "Merge sort"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Database in Full stack development is used to :",
    answer: "Storing and retrieving data",
    options: [
      "Styling HTML pages",
      "Storing and retrieving data",
      "Handling errors on server-side",
      "Rendering web pages"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which data structure is used for implementing recursion?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Stack",
      "Queue",
      "List",
      "Array"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is not the application of stack?",
    answer: "Data Transfer between two asynchronous process",
    options: [
      "A parentheses balancing program",
      "Compiler Syntax Analyzer",
      "Tracking of local variables at run time",
      "Data Transfer between two asynchronous process",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which data structure is needed to convert infix notation to postfix notation?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Tree",
      "Branch",
      "Stack",
      "Queue",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following application makes use of a circular linked list?",
    answer: "Allocating CPU to resources",
    options: [
      "Recursive function calls",
      "Undo operation in a text editor",
      "Implement Hash Tables",
      "Allocating CPU to resources",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the purpose of CSS in Full stack development?",
    answer: "To style and format HTML elements",
    options: [
      "To manage http request and response",
      "To store and retrieve data",
      "To style and format HTML elements",
      "None of the above",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which HTML tag is used to create vector graphics and illustrations?",
    answer: "svg",
    options: [
      "canvas",
      "video",
      "svg",
      "details",
    ]
  },
];

